{
  "inputTimeWaitSecs": 120,
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "84 &times; 454",
      "answer": "38136"
    },
    {
      "question": "-5304 &#xF7; 7",
      "answer": "-5304/7",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "345 &times; 90",
      "answer": "31050"
    },
    {
      "question": "4245 &#xF7; -2",
      "answer": "-4245/2",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "-12 &times; 221",
      "answer": "-2652"
    },
    {
      "question": "-7049 &#xF7; -9",
      "answer": "7049/9",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "1396 &#xF7; 16",
      "answer": "349/4",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "-5248 &#xF7; 10",
      "answer": "-2624/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "-59 &times; 267",
      "answer": "-15753"
    },
    {
      "question": "8020 &#xF7; 3",
      "answer": "8020/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "-87 &times; 119",
      "answer": "-10353"
    },
    {
      "question": "8 &times; -9",
      "answer": "-72"
    },
    {
      "question": "45 &times; -432",
      "answer": "-19440"
    },
    {
      "question": "-480 &times; -53",
      "answer": "25440"
    },
    {
      "question": "-8025 &#xF7; 3",
      "answer": "-2675",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "-151 &times; 44",
      "answer": "-6644"
    },
    {
      "question": "-2899 &#xF7; 10",
      "answer": "-2899/10",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "-97 &times; 333",
      "answer": "-32301"
    },
    {
      "question": "-66 &times; -73",
      "answer": "4818"
    },
    {
      "question": "515 &#xF7; 12",
      "answer": "515/12",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "755 &#xF7; 3",
      "answer": "755/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "-23 &times; 261",
      "answer": "-6003"
    },
    {
      "question": "197 &times; 87",
      "answer": "17139"
    },
    {
      "question": "-44 &times; 109",
      "answer": "-4796"
    },
    {
      "question": "-70 &times; 274",
      "answer": "-19180"
    },
    {
      "question": "-4540 &#xF7; 14",
      "answer": "-2270/7",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "-2676 &#xF7; -9",
      "answer": "892/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "2939 &#xF7; 3",
      "answer": "2939/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "-9170 &#xF7; 3",
      "answer": "-9170/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "21 &times; -82",
      "answer": "-1722"
    },
    {
      "question": "457 &times; 11",
      "answer": "5027"
    },
    {
      "question": "6563 &#xF7; 14",
      "answer": "6563/14",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "337 &times; 73",
      "answer": "24601"
    },
    {
      "question": "2796 &#xF7; 4",
      "answer": "699",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "-4278 &#xF7; 12",
      "answer": "-713/2",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "566 &#xF7; 2",
      "answer": "283",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "6333 &#xF7; 16",
      "answer": "6333/16",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "9664 &#xF7; -14",
      "answer": "-4832/7",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "-16 &times; -10",
      "answer": "160"
    },
    {
      "question": "80 &times; -296",
      "answer": "-23680"
    },
    {
      "question": "-35 &times; -38",
      "answer": "1330"
    },
    {
      "question": "7250 &#xF7; -10",
      "answer": "-725",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "2341 &#xF7; 8",
      "answer": "2341/8",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "96 &times; -314",
      "answer": "-30144"
    },
    {
      "question": "2384 &#xF7; -10",
      "answer": "-1192/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "30 &times; 16",
      "answer": "480"
    },
    {
      "question": "343 &times; -62",
      "answer": "-21266"
    },
    {
      "question": "59 &times; 492",
      "answer": "29028"
    },
    {
      "question": "-6 &times; 57",
      "answer": "-342"
    },
    {
      "question": "9679 &#xF7; -12",
      "answer": "-9679/12",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "-62 &times; -36",
      "answer": "2232"
    },
    {
      "question": "-131 &times; 95",
      "answer": "-12445"
    },
    {
      "question": "-13 &times; 75",
      "answer": "-975"
    },
    {
      "question": "-9613 &#xF7; 14",
      "answer": "-9613/14",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "83 &times; -208",
      "answer": "-17264"
    },
    {
      "question": "1044 &#xF7; -3",
      "answer": "-348",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "-56 &times; -303",
      "answer": "16968"
    },
    {
      "question": "-56 &times; -13",
      "answer": "728"
    },
    {
      "question": "6028 &#xF7; -12",
      "answer": "-1507/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "-45 &times; -241",
      "answer": "10845"
    },
    {
      "question": "319 &times; -53",
      "answer": "-16907"
    },
    {
      "question": "-9392 &#xF7; -5",
      "answer": "9392/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "393 &times; 42",
      "answer": "16506"
    },
    {
      "question": "-36 &times; 76",
      "answer": "-2736"
    },
    {
      "question": "-6125 &#xF7; 14",
      "answer": "-875/2",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "-59 &times; 316",
      "answer": "-18644"
    },
    {
      "question": "-29 &times; 382",
      "answer": "-11078"
    },
    {
      "question": "33 &times; 131",
      "answer": "4323"
    },
    {
      "question": "-6094 &#xF7; -14",
      "answer": "3047/7",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "88 &times; 14",
      "answer": "1232"
    },
    {
      "question": "138 &times; 51",
      "answer": "7038"
    },
    {
      "question": "-51 &times; -20",
      "answer": "1020"
    },
    {
      "question": "416 &times; 95",
      "answer": "39520"
    },
    {
      "question": "-3121 &#xF7; 3",
      "answer": "-3121/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "-80 &times; 310",
      "answer": "-24800"
    },
    {
      "question": "8416 &#xF7; 6",
      "answer": "4208/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "42 &times; -208",
      "answer": "-8736"
    },
    {
      "question": "-1460 &#xF7; 2",
      "answer": "-730",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "562 &#xF7; -11",
      "answer": "-562/11",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "2182 &#xF7; 15",
      "answer": "2182/15",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "143 &times; -73",
      "answer": "-10439"
    },
    {
      "question": "-82 &times; -66",
      "answer": "5412"
    },
    {
      "question": "9551 &#xF7; 14",
      "answer": "9551/14",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "8015 &#xF7; 10",
      "answer": "1603/2",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "56 &times; 324",
      "answer": "18144"
    },
    {
      "question": "-15 &times; -53",
      "answer": "795"
    },
    {
      "question": "43 &times; -233",
      "answer": "-10019"
    },
    {
      "question": "-1888 &#xF7; 10",
      "answer": "-944/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "-279 &times; 47",
      "answer": "-13113"
    },
    {
      "question": "297 &times; -34",
      "answer": "-10098"
    },
    {
      "question": "-3528 &#xF7; 14",
      "answer": "-252",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "49 &times; -27",
      "answer": "-1323"
    },
    {
      "question": "-7587 &#xF7; -15",
      "answer": "2529/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "-8089 &#xF7; 9",
      "answer": "-8089/9",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "152 &times; -80",
      "answer": "-12160"
    },
    {
      "question": "-100 &times; 444",
      "answer": "-44400"
    },
    {
      "question": "-3916 &#xF7; 16",
      "answer": "-979/4",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "467 &times; -46",
      "answer": "-21482"
    },
    {
      "question": "-8171 &#xF7; -10",
      "answer": "8171/10",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "-432 &times; -8",
      "answer": "3456"
    },
    {
      "question": "9159 &#xF7; -4",
      "answer": "-9159/4",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "-7159 &#xF7; -2",
      "answer": "7159/2",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "-68 &times; -88",
      "answer": "5984"
    },
    {
      "question": "-9857 &#xF7; 6",
      "answer": "-9857/6",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "9870 &#xF7; 7",
      "answer": "1410",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "8680 &#xF7; 4",
      "answer": "2170",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "-23 &times; -395",
      "answer": "9085"
    },
    {
      "question": "-9521 &#xF7; 15",
      "answer": "-9521/15",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "-47 &times; 346",
      "answer": "-16262"
    },
    {
      "question": "9623 &#xF7; 10",
      "answer": "9623/10",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "-6980 &#xF7; -10",
      "answer": "698",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "-68 &times; -112",
      "answer": "7616"
    },
    {
      "question": "9245 &#xF7; 2",
      "answer": "9245/2",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "-375 &times; 63",
      "answer": "-23625"
    },
    {
      "question": "-8986 &#xF7; 11",
      "answer": "-8986/11",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "-3403 &#xF7; -4",
      "answer": "3403/4",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "6659 &#xF7; 15",
      "answer": "6659/15",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "7107 &#xF7; 15",
      "answer": "2369/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "-2089 &#xF7; -9",
      "answer": "2089/9",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "30 &times; 350",
      "answer": "10500"
    },
    {
      "question": "-7573 &#xF7; 16",
      "answer": "-7573/16",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "448 &times; 77",
      "answer": "34496"
    },
    {
      "question": "-87 &times; -233",
      "answer": "20271"
    },
    {
      "question": "8 &times; -38",
      "answer": "-304"
    },
    {
      "question": "4548 &#xF7; -4",
      "answer": "-1137",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "-7582 &#xF7; 12",
      "answer": "-3791/6",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "-4194 &#xF7; 13",
      "answer": "-4194/13",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "391 &times; -16",
      "answer": "-6256"
    },
    {
      "question": "1469 &#xF7; 15",
      "answer": "1469/15",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "-202 &#xF7; -4",
      "answer": "101/2",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "-71 &times; 286",
      "answer": "-20306"
    },
    {
      "question": "857 &#xF7; 8",
      "answer": "857/8",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "-471 &times; 75",
      "answer": "-35325"
    },
    {
      "question": "81 &times; -295",
      "answer": "-23895"
    },
    {
      "question": "51 &times; -335",
      "answer": "-17085"
    },
    {
      "question": "125 &times; -63",
      "answer": "-7875"
    },
    {
      "question": "404 &times; -69",
      "answer": "-27876"
    },
    {
      "question": "-343 &times; 50",
      "answer": "-17150"
    },
    {
      "question": "36 &times; -278",
      "answer": "-10008"
    },
    {
      "question": "-344 &times; 24",
      "answer": "-8256"
    },
    {
      "question": "-5871 &#xF7; -5",
      "answer": "5871/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "-28 &times; -168",
      "answer": "4704"
    },
    {
      "question": "-919 &#xF7; 14",
      "answer": "-919/14",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "2681 &#xF7; 5",
      "answer": "2681/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "-425 &times; 71",
      "answer": "-30175"
    },
    {
      "question": "-4864 &#xF7; -13",
      "answer": "4864/13",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "7435 &#xF7; -10",
      "answer": "-1487/2",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "332 &times; -45",
      "answer": "-14940"
    },
    {
      "question": "8 &times; 60",
      "answer": "480"
    },
    {
      "question": "9723 &#xF7; 11",
      "answer": "9723/11",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "8583 &#xF7; 2",
      "answer": "8583/2",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "-7613 &#xF7; -13",
      "answer": "7613/13",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "-77 &times; 40",
      "answer": "-3080"
    },
    {
      "question": "-3431 &#xF7; 7",
      "answer": "-3431/7",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "5707 &#xF7; 12",
      "answer": "5707/12",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "4754 &#xF7; -10",
      "answer": "-2377/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "-4024 &#xF7; 12",
      "answer": "-1006/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "-72 &times; -477",
      "answer": "34344"
    },
    {
      "question": "198 &times; -17",
      "answer": "-3366"
    },
    {
      "question": "-3032 &#xF7; 3",
      "answer": "-3032/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "-12 &times; 79",
      "answer": "-948"
    },
    {
      "question": "270 &times; 39",
      "answer": "10530"
    },
    {
      "question": "210 &times; 6",
      "answer": "1260"
    },
    {
      "question": "-6054 &#xF7; -15",
      "answer": "2018/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "237 &times; 8",
      "answer": "1896"
    },
    {
      "question": "-25 &times; -85",
      "answer": "2125"
    },
    {
      "question": "-6755 &#xF7; -3",
      "answer": "6755/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "-4064 &#xF7; 16",
      "answer": "-254",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "-148 &times; -53",
      "answer": "7844"
    },
    {
      "question": "-24 &times; 434",
      "answer": "-10416"
    },
    {
      "question": "-7493 &#xF7; 6",
      "answer": "-7493/6",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "3126 &#xF7; 3",
      "answer": "1042",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "4967 &#xF7; -5",
      "answer": "-4967/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "362 &times; 45",
      "answer": "16290"
    },
    {
      "question": "2330 &#xF7; 9",
      "answer": "2330/9",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "-429 &times; -87",
      "answer": "37323"
    },
    {
      "question": "9071 &#xF7; -13",
      "answer": "-9071/13",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "3377 &#xF7; 6",
      "answer": "3377/6",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "-131 &#xF7; 11",
      "answer": "-131/11",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "-208 &times; -8",
      "answer": "1664"
    },
    {
      "question": "5977 &#xF7; 12",
      "answer": "5977/12",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "2650 &#xF7; 13",
      "answer": "2650/13",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "-256 &times; 88",
      "answer": "-22528"
    },
    {
      "question": "9412 &#xF7; -3",
      "answer": "-9412/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "113 &times; 46",
      "answer": "5198"
    },
    {
      "question": "3692 &#xF7; 11",
      "answer": "3692/11",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "-83 &times; -249",
      "answer": "20667"
    },
    {
      "question": "1796 &#xF7; 10",
      "answer": "898/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "-187 &times; -58",
      "answer": "10846"
    },
    {
      "question": "2040 &#xF7; -7",
      "answer": "-2040/7",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "-6848 &#xF7; 9",
      "answer": "-6848/9",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "3674 &#xF7; -15",
      "answer": "-3674/15",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "77 &times; -292",
      "answer": "-22484"
    },
    {
      "question": "7777 &#xF7; -5",
      "answer": "-7777/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "9356 &#xF7; -9",
      "answer": "-9356/9",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "5363 &#xF7; 3",
      "answer": "5363/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "-1708 &#xF7; 15",
      "answer": "-1708/15",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "-81 &times; -406",
      "answer": "32886"
    },
    {
      "question": "-2423 &#xF7; -6",
      "answer": "2423/6",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"]
    },
    {
      "question": "-4 &times; 219",
      "answer": "-876"
    }
  ]
}
